♪Mighty winds carry me to the heavens♪
♪On a wild steed,
I sing, smiling at the mortal world♪
♪Then the cold night veils the stars♪
♪I fall to the depths, yet walk alone♪
♪I brave countless snowy peaks♪
♪Your lingering warmth still fills
my palm♪
♪Though frost and snow may bar my way♪
♪The light in my eyes will never fade♪
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
♪I'm still the boy I once was♪
=Sword God=
=Episode 3=
Who are you really?
(Bai Zhi, Lord of the Myriad Demon Hall)
- Greetings, Holy Lord.
Rise.
(Left Protector)
Holy Lord,
(The Myriad Demon Hall)
we haven't heard from you in six months.
(Right Protector)
The two of us
(The Myriad Demon Hall)
sensed your presence
and rushed over at once.
We're so glad you're safe.
If those three hadn't ambushed me,
I wouldn't have spent
all this time recovering.
Holy Lord, to prevent any mishaps,
I suggest you enter seclusion at once
in case the Three Sword Immortals
attack our sect again.
Go into seclusion?
I'd hoped
we could have
a few more quiet decades together.
But I never expected
I'd still have so many ties
I couldn't let go of.
You saved my life,
so I'll give you a great opportunity.
Holy Lord, no!
How can you give your own Dao Bone
to this mortal?
Exactly.
His meridians are damaged.
Your Dao Bone may be
of no use to him.
♪These wounds upon my skin♪
♪Are how the years have crowned me♪
♪Through fading lights,
I finally see it clear♪
I have a thousand Dao Bones.
He saved my life,
so what's wrong with giving him one?
You do have a thousand Dao Bones,
but the one you're giving him
is your strongest sacred-grade Dao Bone.
What makes him worthy of that?
If I say he's worthy,
then he's worthy!
(Take care.)
(I hope one day)
(we'll meet again.)
Bai?
Who?
Who was it?
Why?
Why can't I protect anyone?
(Why is spiritual energy
surging through me?)
(I have a Dao Bone again?)
♪Crossing rivers and seas♪
♪I drink in warmth and cold,
tempering my courage♪
♪Like a firefly
sailing through the night♪
♪My flame is small, yet still it glows♪
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 1)
What's going on with this Dao Bone?
Whose is it?
Why can't I tell what grade it is?
Bai,
I can cultivate again.
Did you see that?
A Tianxuan token...
A warrior from Tianxuan Kingdom.
Looks like Tianxuan Kingdom
is behind this somehow!
Now that I have a Dao Bone,
I need to transform my meridians
and cleanse my marrow soon,
and heal my old injuries.
The Heavenly Sword Sect's Alchemy Hall
would be a good place to do it.
I need to become a formal disciple soon.
(Cuihua, Heavenly Sword Sect
Servant Disciple)
Senior Brother Zhao.
Don't call me Senior Brother.
We're both servant disciples.
Others might hear and cause trouble.
All right then.
Take this,
Senior Brother Zhao...
I made it myself.
It's for you.
It's really good.
Just take it.
Thank you.
What are you guys up to?
Don't get the wrong idea, Zhao Feiyang.
We had no idea
you were the fiancé
of the Holy Maiden of Tianxuan Kingdom.
We offended you before.
Here.
These spirit crystals
are our way of apologizing.
(Is this because of Chen Qiushui?)
I don't need them.
Zhao Feiyang,
don't be so ungrateful!
Get lost!
Fine.
Fine. You win.
- Let's go.
- Just you wait!
Sorry, Holy Maiden.
That guy
wouldn't have it.
Forget it.
You may leave.
Alright.
We wish you success
in obtaining the divine-grade Dao Bone.
Once you do,
please look out for us.
Sure.
What's wrong with Qingzhu?
She went to kill some village woman
and ended up going missing herself.
Forget it.
Once I claim that divine-grade Dao Bone,
I'll go find her.
(The Day the Dao Bone Emerges)
Today,
a divine-grade Dao Bone
has emerged in our sect.
(Heavenly Sword Sect)
Who will ultimately claim it
has yet to be decided.
It all comes down to strength
and fate.
(Wang Feng, Heavenly Sword Sect Master)
Activate the formation!
♪I once stood on high,
drawing spiritual energy into my blade♪
♪I laughed, pointing at the stars,
young and fearless♪
♪Then came my fall,
with frost and snow on my shoulders♪
♪My Dao foundation was damaged,
yet my Dao heart never wavered♪
♪I crossed countless peaks
to find my answer again♪
♪Through endless trials,
my Nascent Soul came♪
♪Heaven and earth my furnace,
I rose from the flame♪
♪No sword in hand,
yet numberless blades obey♪
♪I seek the Dao beyond the clouds♪
♪Unafraid of countless trials♪
♪With this flesh and soul♪
♪I shall forge a new age♪
♪Let thunder and fire crown me♪
♪Let wind and clouds heed me♪
♪At cultivation's peak♪
♪My first resolve remains unchanged♪
♪The sun and moon turn♪
♪I hear the Great Dao ring♪
♪I am the undying flame♪
♪Looking back when dust settles♪
♪At last I see, immortality♪
♪Lives in your smiles.♪